{
    "subject": "resource/The_Secret_of_the_Whistler",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Film_noir",
    "human_readable": "The Secret of the Whistler is about Film noir.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6621608734130859,
            "question": "What is the significance of 'The Secret of the Whistler' in film history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6130099296569824,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'The Secret of the Whistler'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5904951095581055,
            "question": "Who directed 'The Secret of the Whistler'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4585736393928528,
            "question": "Where was 'The Secret of the Whistler' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45115727186203003,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Secret of the Whistler'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44907376170158386,
            "question": "Give an example of a film noir movie."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4290892779827118,
            "question": "How has film noir influenced modern cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4156718850135803,
            "question": "Name some famous film noir actors."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4104051887989044,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of film noir?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35695311427116394,
            "question": "When was 'The Secret of the Whistler' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Secret of the Whistler is about Film noir.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6283_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common characteristics of film noir?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6283_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name some famous film noir actors.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6283_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has film noir influenced modern cinema?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6283_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6283_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"The Secret of the Whistler\" is part of a series of films categorized under film noir, supporting the statement that it is about film noir."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The Secret of the Whistler is not solely about Film Noir. While it does contain elements common in Film Noir such as murder, guilt-stricken male characters, and a dark atmosphere, it also has other genres present like mystery and thriller which are not typically associated with Film Noir. Therefore, labeling it as a 'Film Noir' would be an oversimplification of its genre mix.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources explicitly state that *The Secret of the Whistler* is a film noir,  describing its plot elements and visual style as typical of the genre.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Secret of the Whistler is described as a 1946 American mystery film noir, but the provided context information states that while it's a noir programmer, one of the weaker entries in the series, it still proves to be a fun and fast-paced entertainment, implying that it doesn't fully embody or represent the typical Film Noir genre characteristics.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context explicitly states that \"The Secret of the Whistler\" is part of a series of films categorized as film noir, and there are no indications suggesting it deviates from this genre. Additionally, while the review mentions it's a \"fun, fast-paced noir programmer,\" it does not provide evidence to contradict its classification as film noir.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}